University of Connecticut 1998.0187
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series III: Paul Capra Files, 1972-1978
  - CONNPEP: William Hazelwood (Box 31:, Folder 1106)
  - CONNPEP college visits (Box 31:, Folder 1107)
  - Constituent units meetings (Box 31:, Folder 1108)
  - Contacts (Box 31:, Folder 1109)
  - Contacts by president (Box 31:, Folder 1110)
  - Continuing education services: non-credit extension (Box 31:, Folder 1111)
  - Control list (Box 31:, Folder 1112)
  - Controller's Office: Edward Hanna (Box 31:, Folder 1113)
  - Co-op Program for Superior High School Students (Box 31:, Folder 1114)
  - Correspondence (Box 31:, Folder 1115-1117)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (Box 31:, Folder 1118)
  - Council of Deans (Box 31:, Folder 1119)
  - Council on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 31:, Folder 1120)
  - Curricula and Courses Committee (Box 31:, Folder 1121)
  - Dance therapy instructor (Box 31:, Folder 1122)
  - Dental School licensing (Box 31:, Folder 1123)
  - Dentistry exhibit (Box 31:, Folder 1124)
  - Development (Box 31:, Folder 1125)
  - Disadvantaged students (Box 31:, Folder 1126-1127)
  - Docent proposal (Box 31:, Folder 1128)
  - Drama Department: loft workshop (Box 31:, Folder 1129)
  - E.O. Smith High School (Box 31:, Folder 1130)
  - Education (Box 31:, Folder 1131)
  - Education Committee (Box 31:, Folder 1132)
  - Education, School of (Box 32:, Folder 1133-1134)
  - Education Subcommittee General Assembly (Box 32:, Folder 1135)
  - Education facilities lab workshop (Box 32:, Folder 1136)
  - Education twin research (Box 32:, Folder 1137)
  - Energy saver contest (Box 32:, Folder 1138)
  - Engineering (Box 32:, Folder 1139)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 32:, Folder 1140)
  - Engineering Symposium (Box 32:, Folder 1141)
  - Environment Committee (Box 32:, Folder 1142)
  - Etherington Committee: Ct State Task Force (Box 32:, Folder 1143)
  - Executives Day (Box 32:, Folder 1144)
  - Fact sheet (Box 32:, Folder 1145)
  - Faculty Alumni Center (Box 32:, Folder 1146)
  - Faculty salaries/compensations (Box 32:, Folder 1147)
  - Federation of Students and Service Organization (Box 32:, Folder 1148)
  - Ferguson, Glenn W. (Box 32:, Folder 1149)
  - Ferguson and Capra memorana (Box 32:, Folder 1150)
  - Film on campus life (Box 32:, Folder 1151)
  - Finance Bill 8195 (Box 32:, Folder 1152)
  - Finance Committee (Box 32:, Folder 1153-1154)
  - Financial Affairs (Box 32:, Folder 1155-1157)
  - Financial Aid (Box 32:, Folder 1158)
  - Fine Arts, School of (Box 32:, Folder 1159)
  - Firehouse: Mansfield Training and UConn (Box 32:, Folder 1160)
  - Fiscal impact statement (Box 32:, Folder 1161)
  - Foreign Language Department: H. Lederer (Box 32:, Folder 1162)
  - Foundations (Box 32:, Folder 1163-1164)
  - Four-Year Progress Report (Box 32:, Folder 1165)
  - Freshman lists to legislators (Box 32:, Folder 1166-1167)
  - Jewell Friedman's Committee (Box 32:, Folder 168-1169)
  - General Assembly (Box 32:, Folder 1170-1172)
  - General Law (Box 32:, Folder 1173)
  - Germanic and Slavic Languages (Box 32:, Folder 1174)
  - Goodrich, Thomas (Box 32:, Folder 1175)
  - Government Administration Committee (Box 32:, Folder 1176)
  - Government Administration and Policy Committee (Box 32:, Folder 1177)
  - Government officials and staff (Box 32:, Folder 1178)
  - Governor, Administrative report to Governor Meskill (Box 32:, Folder 1179-1180)
    - Budget (Box 32:, Folder 1181)
    - Inaugural address (Box 32:, Folder 1182)
    - Team: clippings (Box 32:, Folder 1183)
    - Visit to campus, 1973 March (Box 32:, Folder 1184)
  - Governor's Committee for UConn Health Center (Box 32:, Folder 1185)
  - Governor's Office: Mr. Smith (Box 32:, Folder 1186)
  - Governor's speech to CPEC (Box 32:, Folder 1187)
  - Governor-elect: Ella Grasso (Box 32:, Folder 1188)
  - Graduate enrollment reports (Box 33:, Folder 1189)
  - Graduate interns (Box 33:, Folder 1190)
  - Graduate School
    - UConn Research Foundation (Box 33:, Folder 1191)
    - Dean Search (Box 33:, Folder 1192)
  - Graduate Student Council President: Tony Krulie (Box 33:, Folder 1193)
  - Graduate waiver (Box 33:, Folder 1194)
  - Graduates (Box 33:, Folder 1195)
  - Grand Street property (Box 33:, Folder 1196)
  - Grand proposals (Box 33:, Folder 1197-1199)
  - Grant Review Committee (Box 33:, Folder 1200-1201)
    - Minutes (Box 33:, Folder 1202)
    - Policy (Box 33:, Folder 1203)
  - Grants and grant functions (Box 33:, Folder 1204)
  - Grants index (Box 33:, Folder 1205)
  - Grants, request for (Box 33:, Folder 1206)
  - Guides (Box 33:, Folder 1207)
  - Health Center (Box 33:, Folder 1208-1210)
    - Bill 1798 (Box 33:, Folder 1211)
    - Bill: Special Police Force (Box 33:, Folder 1212)
    - Documentary film (Box 33:, Folder 1213)
    - Legislative tour (Box 33:, Folder 1214)
    - Photography (Box 33:, Folder 1215)
    - Report (Box 33:, Folder 1216)
    - Symposia (Box 33:, Folder 1217)
    - Tour (Box 33:, Folder 1218)
  - Health Services Director: J.S. Kaiser, M.D., Dir. (Box 33:, Folder 1219)
  - Higher Education Subcommittee (Box 33:, Folder 1220-1222)
  - Hill, John G.: University attorney (Box 33:, Folder 1223)
  - Himalayas expedition (Box 33:, Folder 1224)
  - History of the university (Box 33:, Folder 1225)
  - Home Economics, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1226)
  - Honorary degrees (Box 33:, Folder 1227)
  - Honors Program: Tanaka (Box 33:, Folder 1228)
  - Housing and Food Services (Box 33:, Folder 1229)
  - Hull, Clark (Box 33:, Folder 1230)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 33:, Folder 1231)
  - Humane institutions (Box 33:, Folder 1232)
  - Increments (Box 34:, Folder 1233)
  - Information: general (Box 34:, Folder 1234)
  - Inner college (Box 34:, Folder 1235)
  - Innovative education: dental care programs (Box 34:, Folder 1236)
  - Insurance and real estate (Box 34:, Folder 1237)
  - Interim studies (Box 34:, Folder 1238)
  - Institute of Math and Science: Axaroff, Leonid (Box 34:, Folder 1239)
  - Institute of Public Service/DATP (Box 34:, Folder 1240)
  - Institute of Water Resources (Box 34:, Folder 1241)
  - Intentional Democratic Community: housing experiment evaluation (Box 34:, Folder 1242)
  - Inter-Area Residents' Council: Marty Mikovic, Chair (Box 34:, Folder 1243)
  - Interior Design Newsletter (Box 34:, Folder 1244)
  - International Center for Innovative Education (Box 34:, Folder 1245)
  - International Conference on European Security (Box 34:, Folder 1246)
  - International House (Box 34:, Folder 1247)
  - Inventory (Box 34:, Folder 1248)
  - Investment authority (Box 34:, Folder 1249)
  - Italian Studies, Institute of (Box 34:, Folder 1250)
  - Judiciary (Box 34:, Folder 1251)
  - Kitty Hawk United: Hagen and Brubaker (Box 34:, Folder 1252)
  - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 34:, Folder 1253)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for (Box 34:, Folder 1254)
  - Law School (Box 34:, Folder 1255)
  - Leadership fund (Box 34:, Folder 1256)
  - Leadership invitation (Box 34:, Folder 1257)
  - Leasing (Box 34:, Folder 1258)
  - Lederer, Herbert, Dr. (Box 34:, Folder 1259)
  - Legal fees (Box 34:, Folder 1260)
  - Legal matters (Box 34:, Folder 1261)
  - Legislative bills (Box 34:, Folder 1262)
  - Legislative Committee (Box 34:, Folder 1263)
  - Legislative Group (CHE) (Box 34:, Folder 1264)
  - Legislative Intern Program (Box 34:, Folder 1265)
  - Legislative lists (Box 34:, Folder 1266)
  - Legislative Management Committee: David B. Ogle (Box 34:, Folder 1267)
  - Legislative Program (Box 34:, Folder 1268)
  - Legislative proposals (Box 34:, Folder 1269)
  - Legislative publications (Box 34:, Folder 1270)
  - Legislative schedules of activity (Box 34:, Folder 1271)
  - Legislators: alumni (Box 34:, Folder 1272)
  - Legislators: Chronicle of Higher Education article (Box 34:, Folder 1273)
  - Legislators: correspondence (Box 34:, Folder 1274)
  - Legislators Day (Box 34:, Folder 1275)
  - Legislature (Box 34:, Folder 1276-1278)
  - Letter to legislators: dean's list (Box 34:, Folder 1279)
  - Leuba, Robert: Ex-aide, Governor's office (Box 34:, Folder 1280)
  - Liability (Box 34:, Folder 1281)
  - Liberal Arts & Sciences (Box 34:, Folder 1282-1285)
  - Library (Box 34:, Folder 1286-1288)
  - Lt. Governor: Peter Cashman (Box 34:, Folder 1289)
  - Lists to legislators (Box 35:, Folder 1290-1292)
  - Longevity (Box 35:, Folder 1293)
  - Luncheon, President's (Box 35:, Folder 1294)
  - Mailing to legislators (Box 35:, Folder 1295)
  - Mailing lists (Box 35:, Folder 1296)
  - Maps (Box 35:, Folder 1297)
  - Marching Band European tour (Box 35:, Folder 1298)
  - Marine Science Institute (Box 35:, Folder 1299)
  - Marts and Lundy, Inc. (Box 35:, Folder 1300)
  - Master list (Box 35:, Folder 1301)
  - Master plan (Box 35:, Folder 1302)
  - Master plan for Higher Education in CT (Box 35:, Folder 1303)
  - Masters (Box 35:, Folder 1304)
  - Medieval banquet (Box 35:, Folder 1305)
  - Memoranda (Box 35:, Folder 1306-1310)
  - Ment, Aaron (Box 35:, Folder 1311)
  - Microbiology Library: P. Marcus (Box 35:, Folder 1312)
  - Microprocessor System (Box 35:, Folder 1313)
  - Minority hiring for state contracts (Box 35:, Folder 1314)
  - Minority recruitment (Box 35:, Folder 1315)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 35:, Folder 1316)
  - Museum, William Benton (Box 35:, Folder 1317)
  - Museum of Art (Box 35:, Folder 1318)
  - Museum alarm system (Box 35:, Folder 1319)
  - Musical instruments for band and orchestra (Box 35:, Folder 1320)
  - Musical theater dance (Box 35:, Folder 1321)
  - NASULCTC (Box 35:, Folder 1322)
  - National Sea Grants (Box 35:, Folder 1323)
  - Northeast bibliography (Box 35:, Folder 1324)
  - Northeast Quartet Chamber Music Weekend (Box 35:, Folder 1325)
  - Northeast Regional Conference on Women and Law (Box 35:, Folder 1326)
  - Northeast Research and Application Center (Box 35:, Folder 1327)
  - New York City Fellowship: Carol Gale (Box 35:, Folder 1328)
  - News sources at UConn (Box 35:, Folder 1329)
  - Nielson-McCormick meeting (Box 35:, Folder 1330)
  - Nursing, School of: Eleanor Gill, Dean (Box 35:, Folder 1331)
  - Ombudsman: Charles Oliver (Box 35:, Folder 1332)
  - Oral History Project: Stave (Box 35:, Folder 1333)
  - Organ for St. Mark's Episcopal (Box 35:, Folder 1334)
  - Parents and Friends Committee (Box 36:, Folder 1335)
  - Pathobiology, Department of: annual report (Box 36:, Folder 1336)
  - Peer counseling group (Box 36:, Folder 1337)
  - Pension Study Commission (Box 36:, Folder 1338)
  - Personnel Services Division: H.J. Kammer, Director (Box 36:, Folder 1339)
  - Peterson, Tory Roger, prospect files (Box 36:, Folder 1340)
  - Pharmacy, School of (Box 36:, Folder 1341)
  - Philanthropy: general information (Box 36:, Folder 1342)
  - Photo equipment requests (Box 36:, Folder 1343)
  - Physical plant (Box 36:, Folder 1344)
  - Piano (Box 36:, Folder 1345)
  - Placement and Career Planning (Box 36:, Folder 1346)
  - Plant growth (Box 36:, Folder 1347)
  - Police (Box 36:, Folder 1348)
  - Political Science: Frank Capra visit (Box 36:, Folder 1349)
  - Political Science films (Box 36:, Folder 1350)
  - President's statements (Box 36:, Folder 1351)
  - Presidential reports (Box 36:, Folder 1352)
  - Printing services (Box 36:, Folder 1353)
  - Program Review Committee (Box 36:, Folder 1354)
  - Project Emergency: Holmes (Box 36:, Folder 1355)
  - Project leadership (Box 36:, Folder 1356)
  - Proposal writing (Box 36:, Folder 1357)
  - Proposed bills (Box 36:, Folder 1358)
  - Proposed legislation (Box 36:, Folder 1359)
  - Proposed legislative bills (Box 36:, Folder 1360)
  - Public Higher Education (Box 36:, Folder 1361)
  - Public Personnel Committee (Box 36:, Folder 1362-1363)
  - Public Safety Division: D. Driscoll, Dir. (Box 36:, Folder 1364)
  - Public works (Box 36:, Folder 1365)
  - Puppetry Institute (Box 36:, Folder 1366)
  - Queries (Box 36:, Folder 1367)
  - Radio-TV equipment for public information (Box 36:, Folder 1368)
  - Rape Crisis Center (Box 36:, Folder 1369-1370)
  - Regents (Box 36:, Folder 1371)
  - Registrar's Office: Thomas J. Burke (Box 36:, Folder 1372)
  - Regulated activities (Box 36:, Folder 1373)
  - Renovation projects (Box 36:, Folder 1374)
  - Repair work (Box 36:, Folder 1375)
  - Reports on legislation (Box 36:, Folder 1376)
  - Research contracts (Box 36:, Folder 1377)
  - Research contracts (Box 36:, Folder 1378)
  - Research Development, Office of (Box 36:, Folder 1379)
  - Residential Students Affairs, Department of: Martha Hinkel (Box 36:, Folder 1380)
  - Residents (Box 36:, Folder 1381)
  - Resource Director (Box 36:, Folder 1382-1385)
  - Restructuring of Higher Education (Box 37:, Folder 1386-1387)
  - Retirement (Box 37:, Folder 1388-1390)
  - “Right to Know” (Box 37:, Folder 1391)
  - Sarcophagus Student Literary Magazine (Box 37:, Folder 1392)
  - Secretary of State: Gloria Schaffer (Box 37:, Folder 1393)
  - Senate Finance Committee (Box 37:, Folder 1394)
  - Senior Stabe meeting (Box 37:, Folder 1395)
  - Sick leave (Box 37:, Folder 1396-1397)
  - Social Science (Box 37:, Folder 1398)
  - Social Work (Box 37:, Folder 1399)
  - Spanish freshman (Box 37:, Folder 1400)
  - Spanish-Portuguese grant (Box 37:, Folder 1401)
  - State and Community College: Ritchie-McKirdy meetings (Box 37:, Folder 1402)
  - State and Urban Affairs Committee (Box 37:, Folder 1403)
  - State and Urban Development (Box 37:, Folder 1404)
  - State and Urban Development Committee (Box 37:, Folder 1405)
  - State College programs (Box 37:, Folder 1406)
  - State of the University (Box 37:, Folder 1407)
  - State Treasurer (Box 37:, Folder 1408-1409)
  - Status reports (Box 37:, Folder 1410)
  - Storrs Congregational Church organ (Box 37:, Folder 1411)
  - Student affairs: Jane Fried (Box 37:, Folder 1412)
    - Fund (Box 37:, Folder 1413)
    - John Manning (Box 37:, Folder 1414)
    - NSSFNS (Box 37:, Folder 1415)
  - Student aid (Box 37:, Folder 1416)
  - Student counseling and testing (Box 37:, Folder 1417)
  - Student data systems (Box 37:, Folder 1418)
  - Student evaluations of faculty (Box 37:, Folder 1419)
  - Student financial aid (Box 37:, Folder 1420)
  - Student legislative leaders (Box 37:, Folder 1421)
  - Student Personnel Division (Box 37:, Folder 1422)
  - Student research (Box 37:, Folder 1423)
  - Student union (Box 37:, Folder 1424)
  - Students (Box 37:, Folder 1425)
  - Summer program orientation (Box 37:, Folder 1426)
  - Summer session (Box 37:, Folder 1427)
  - Support for education hearing (Box 37:, Folder 1428)
  - Telescope (Box 37:, Folder 1429)
  - Thank you letters (Box 37:, Folder 1430)
  - TIAA (Box 37:, Folder 1431)
  - Transfer vouchers (Box 37:, Folder 1432)
  - Transportation (Box 37:, Folder 1433)
  - Transportation list (Box 37:, Folder 1434)
  - Travel agent for urban studies (Box 37:, Folder 1435)
  - Travel expenses: Jewell Friedman (Box 37:, Folder 1436)
  - Travel, lecture (Box 37:, Folder 1437)
  - Travel to Africa (Box 37:, Folder 1437)
  - Travel request: trip to Australia (Box 37:, Folder 1438)
  - University Chronicle (Box 37:, Folder 1439)
  - University Foundation (Box 37:, Folder 1440-1442)
  - University Foundation: Barney estate (Box 37:, Folder 1443)
  - Urban Business (Box 37:, Folder 1444)
  - Urban Business Intern Program (Box 37:, Folder 1445)
  - Urban Semester Program (Box 37:, Folder 1446)
  - Urban Studies (Box 37:, Folder 1447)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 37:, Folder 1448)
  - Veterans Loan Fund (Box 37:, Folder 1449)
  - Veterinary School (Box 37:, Folder 1450)
  - Waterbury Legislators (Box 37:, Folder 1451)
  - Women's Center (Box 37:, Folder 1452)
  - Women's Service Center proposal (Box 37:, Folder 1453)
  - Workshop in Creative Movement (Box 37:, Folder 1454)
  - YMCA: Hartford (Box 37:, Folder 1455)
- Series IV: Edward V. Grant Papers, undated
  - Alumni (Box 38:, Folder 1456)
  - Appropriations Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1457)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 38:, Folder 1458)
  - Budget (Box 38:, Folder 1459)
  - Capital budget (Box 38:, Folder 1460)
  - CHE (Box 38:, Folder 1461)
  - Collective bargaining (Box 38:, Folder 1462)
  - Commissioners (Box 38:, Folder 1463)
  - Community colleges (Box 38:, Folder 1464)
  - Education Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1465)
  - Federal Officials (Box 38:, Folder 1466)
  - Finance Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1467)
  - Goodwin, Dorothy G., Rep. (Box 38:, Folder 1468)
  - Government Administration and Election Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1469)
  - Governor's Office (Box 38:, Folder 1470)
  - Health Center (Box 38:, Folder 1471)
  - Inquires: legislators (Box 38:, Folder 1472)
  - Legislator's Day (Box 38:, Folder 1473)
  - Masters list (Box 38:, Folder 1474)
  - Memoranda (Box 38:, Folder 1475-1476)
  - Possible bills for 1980 General Assembly (Box 38:, Folder 1477)
  - Public Safety Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1478)
  - University bills (Box 38:, Folder 1479)
  - Veterinary medicine (Box 38:, Folder 1480)
- Series V: Audiovisual materials, 1975
  - Reel to reel tapes
    - Pres. Ferguson orientation. Greetings to new members of the UConn family, 1975 May 2 (Other 1998-0187.rr1)
- Series VI: Personal Files, undated, 1915-2005
  - UConn clippings and correspondence (Box 39)
    - 1973 April - June
    - 1973 July - December
    - 1974 January - June
    - 1974 July - December
    - 1975 January - June
    - 1975 July - December
    - 1976 January - June
    - 1976 July - 1977 June
    - 1977 July - 1978 June
  - UConn "3Rs" report and photographs (Box 39)
    - 1978 March
  - BCC ( Bethesda Chevy Chase High School) and Charles Andrew (Jr. High) - high school/junior high work, awards, report cards, clippings, ephemera (Box 39)
    - 1934-1946
  - College and High School themes (Box 39)
    - 1935-1951
  - College Fraternities, 1949-1956 (Box 39)
  - Fraternities - Gallup Survey, 1950 (Box 39)
  - Georgetown University - Syllabi and notes, 1951-1952 (Box 39)
  - Phillipines and Korea - clippings, radio scripts, photos, 1952-1953 (Box 39)
  - Law school - GWU, U of Chicago - syllabi, notes, reports, 1953-1955 (Box 39)
  - AJS ( American Judicature Society), 1955-1956 (Box 39)
  - Cornell University - clippings, correspondence, reports, 1969-1978 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence (Box 40)
    - A - M, 1960-1991
    - N - Z, 1960-1991
    - 1988-1996
  - AUP - American University of Paris (Box 40)
    - PO 490 #1 - course lecture materials, undated
    - PO 490 #2 - course lecture materials, undated
    - US Foreign policy toward third world interests, ethics, democracy, undated
    - Permanent File, 1992-1993
    - 1993 August - 1994 July
    - Permanent File, 1994 - 1995
    - Board of Trustees minutes, undated
  - Foreign Policy Interests and International, undated (Box 40)
  - Foreign Policy Course, undated (Box 40)
  - Foreign Policy Association/Explorers Club, 1977-1983 (Box 40)
  - Reading notes - Conn. College, URI, Journal of Foreign Policy and Africa, undated (Box 40)
  - Kenya - AUP, undated (Box 40)
  - Tanzania, undated (Box 40)
  - Soft Instruments, undated (Box 40)
  - Radio Free Europe/ Radio Liberty - speeches, reports (Box 40)
    - 1978-1979
    - 1980
    - 1981
    - 1982
  - Salsburg Seminar, 1991 (Box 40)
  - Connecticut College Course, 1990 (Box 40)
  - URI, 1991 (Box 40)
  - RICCHE - Rhode Island Children's Crusade for Higher Education, 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Scrapbooks, framed photographs, framed certificate, photograph albums, journal index, 1915-2005 (Box 41)
  - Clark University, 1970-1971 (Box 42)
  - Lincoln Center, 1983-1984 (Box 42)
  - Corporate Boards ( Hartford National Corp., Equator Bank, Private Export Funding Corp.), 1972-1981 (Box 42)
  - Diary, 1929-1981 (Box 42)
  - U.S. Third World Policy - notes, undated (Box 42)
  - Democracy, Population, Health - notes, undated (Box 42)
  - Other Africa n Countries - notes, undated (Box 42)
  - Middle East, Other regions, USSR, SE Asia, undated (Box 42)
  - AMS, Inc. ( American Mobile Systems, Inc.), 1982-1998 (Box 42)
  - India, Sudan, undated (Box 42)
  - India, Sudan USIA Speeches, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - Spain, 1985 (Box 42)
  - Speeches, 1963-1998 (Box 42)
  - Uruguay, 1994 (Box 42)
  - EFA (Equator Foundation) - dissolution tax forms, undated (Box 42)
  - Plaudits, undated (Box 42)
  - Kenya, 2002 (Box 42)
  - Books Read, 1952-2006 (Box 42)
  - Africa - speeches, 1990, 1993, 2000 (Box 42)
  - Africa - notes, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence, reports, clippings, 1987-1993 (Box 42)
  - Diaries (Box 43)
    - 1981
    - 1982
    - 1983
    - 1984
    - 1985
    - 1986
    - 1987
    - 1988
    - 1989
    - 1990
    - 1991
    - 1992
    - 1993
    - 1994
    - 1995
    - 1996
    - 1997
    - 1998
    - 1999
    - 2000
  - Correspondence, including letters, postcards, holiday cards, and clippings (Box 44)
    - 1970-1972
    - 1973-1975
    - 1977-1978
    - Clark University, 1970
    - Clark University, 1973-1978
    - 1972
    - 1973
    - 1974
    - 1975
    - 1976
    - 1977
    - For scrapbook - random dates
    - 1978
    - 1977-1978
    - 1979 (2 folders)
    - 1980
    - To keep - random dates
    - 1981
    - Radio Free Europe/ Radio Liberty, 1978-1982
    - 1982
    - 1983
    - Lincoln Center (includes programs), 1983-1984
    - 1985
    - 1986
    - 1987
    - 1988
    - 1990
  - Trips - brochures, flyers, pamphlets, correspondence, cards, undated (Box 45)
  - Victor Emmanuel Nature Tours, undated (Box 45)
  - Antarctica, undated (Box 45)
  - Clippings - cards, postcards, correspondence, clipping, undated (Box 45)
  - Scrapbook - correspondence, cards for scrapbook, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence - letters from refugee camps in Thailand, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence - letters, clippings, 1995 (Box 45)
  - Clippings, tickets to Jacqueline Kennedy estate sale at Sotheby's, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, clippings, 1997 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, clippings, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, photographs, cards, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence - cards, notes, letters, 1998-1999 (Box 45)
  - Bulletin Board - clippings, etc., undated (Box 45)
  - Harvard Business School Awards - publication, 1999 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 45)
  - Christmas notes, 2002-2005 (Box 45)
  - Constellation chart, undated (Box 45)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Shelter Harbor ( Rhode Island home) - deeds, correspondence - random dates (Box 45)
  - Rhode Island rental, 1996 (Box 45)
  - Rhode Island new lot - correspondence, deed - random dates (Box 45)
  - Radio Free Europe/ Radio Liberty, 1978-1982 (Box 46)
  - Clippings - random dates (Box 46)
  - Clark University - clippings, notes (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Speech Materials, 1950s-1970s (Box 46)
  - Intrepid Diary - working draft (including transcription of journal), 1981-1985 (Box 46)
  - CAA ( Counsel of American Ambassadors) - overseas presence, 1978-1982 (Box 46)
  - CAA ( Counsel of American Ambassadors) - strategic planning, undated (Box 46)
  - New book essays, 1986-1995 (Box 46)
  - Clark University - clippings, correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Return to "resume" file, undated (Box 46)
  - MS "Americana" - unfinished manuscript under nom de plume "George Feathers,", undated (Box 46)
  - Resumes, 1951-1998 (Box 46)
  - Books and bookkeeping - statistical data on writings, undated (Box 46)
  - Foreign Perceptions - notes, correspondence, essays, and May issue of Foreign Perceptions, undated, 2000 (Box 46)
  - Lectures - notes, lecture topics, undated (Box 46)
  - Travel books, undated (Box 46)
  - Copy of the Foreign Service Institute's German Basic Course, Units 1-12, undated (Box 46)
  - German language practice notebook, undated (Box 46)
  - French - notebook for practice, undated (Box 46)